افسحوا الطريق!
Our leader is here!
لكنها لم تعد بعد.She left for school this morning,
مالاياراسان وكوتاياراسان.The reason behind this are the brothers,
بأكلمها بالماء والخمور.
يا إلهي!
Oh god!
سينجارام، لا يمكنك الركل أو الاحتفاظ!
Singaram, you can’t kick or keep!
توقف، سيدي! لقد جاء في الوسط،
Stop it, sir! He came in between,
وإلا، لكان ذلك هدفًا مثاليًا.
otherwise, that would’ve been
a perfect goal.
إذا كانت لديك شكوك،
فلنخض جولة أخرى!
If you have doubts,
let’s go one more round!
-لماذا؟ لتقتلنا جميعًا؟
-حسنًا، خذوه بعيدًا.
-Why? To kill us all?
-Alright, take him away.
-نعم، دكتور. في الطريق.
-هيا، أسرع!
-Yes, doctor. We're on the way.
-Come on, hurry up!
مهلاً! لقد وصلت للتو.
Hey! You’ve just arrived.
لا حاجة لإنجاز كل شيء في يوم واحد.
No need to do everything in one day.
هذه ملكيتي.
ابق هنا.
That’s my property.
Stay here.
لنذهب!
Let's go!
احذر. هناك خطوات.
Be careful. There are steps.
بفضل معلم الرياضيات،
أصبحت لدي فرصة للتقرب من سوجي.
Thanks to the Maths teacher,
I now have a chance to woo Suji.
اتجه مباشرة.
Go straight.
احذري! احذري، سوجي…
Careful! Careful, Suji…
ماذا؟ لماذا تعود في مسار معكوس؟
Huh? Why is she taking a U-turn?
سوجي! سوجي!
Suji! Suji!
لماذا تمزقين
ملصقات الرئيس؟!
Why are you tearing down
the Chairman’s posters?!
--إنهم أشرار.
انظر، يا سيدي!
-They’re bad people.
-Look, sir!
لقد لصقوا ملصقاتهم
على إعلان راميا.
They’ve pasted their posters
over Ramya’s notice.
-اللعنة، هذا ممتع.
-هل هذا عادل، يا سيدي؟
-Damn, it feels good.
-Is this fair, sir?
لا، ليس كذلك.
No, it’s not.
هذا ظلم!
فظائع!
It’s injustice!
Atrocity!
راقبني—سأمزق كل شيء.
Watch me—I’ll tear everything down.
لن أدع هذا يمر مرور الكرام!
I won’t let this slide!
أمل، انظري هناك.
Amal, look there.
-لا يبقى ملصق بعد كلمة سوجي!
-مهلاً! توقف.
-No poster stays after my Suji’s word!
-Hey! Stop it.
سأمزقهم جميعًا!
I’ll tear it all down!
لماذا تمزقين ملصق رئيسنا؟
Why are you tearing down
our boss’s poster?
لأنني أريد ذلك!
من أنت حتى تسألني؟
Because I want to!
Who are you to question me?
-تجرئين؟!
-نعم!
-You dare?!
-Yes!
-ماذا قلت للتو؟
-لا أكرر كلامي.
-What did you just say?
-I don’t repeat myself.
-مهلاً! قلت له أن يفعلها.
-ماذا؟ أنت من أمرته؟!
-Hey! I told him to do it.
-What? You told him to?!
يا إلهي، مع بعض العظام
وقليل من الدم،
Oh god, with just some bones
and a little blood,
هي تخوض صراعًا مع
هؤلاء الحيوانات البرية؟
she’s picking a fight with
these wild animals?
لماذا فعلت ذلك؟
Why did you do that?
هذه مستشفى!
الناس يأتون ويذهبون.
This is a hospital!
People come and go.
إذا علّقت إعلان راميا هنا،
سيراه المزيد من الناس.
If I stick Ramya’s notice here,
more people will see it.
سيساعدنا ذلك في العثور عليها أسرع!
It’ll help us find her faster!
وقد لصقتم ملصق رئيسكم فوقه!
And you pasted your boss’s poster over it!
-مهلاً! سنلصقه حيثما نريد!
-Hey! We’ll paste it wherever we want!
هو ليس مجرد رئيس مدرسة
—إنه يمتلك هذه المدينة بأكملها!
He’s not just a school chairman
—he owns this whole town!
نعم، هذا ما يحدث عندما
يتحول المجرم المتهم إلى رئيس!
Yeah, that’s what happens when
an accused criminal becomes a chairman!
اللعنة!
Damn!
الفظائع التي ترتكبها في
هذه المدينة لن تدوم إلى الأبد.
The atrocities you commit in
this town won’t last forever.
يا إلهي!
Oh god!
أعمل على وضع حد لهذا!
I'm working to put an end to this!
إذا استمريت في هذا الهراء!
If you keep up this nonsense!
اللعنة، يجب أن أنقذ فتاتي!
Damn, I’ve got to save my girl!
مهلاً! انتظر، انتظر.
Hey! Hold on, hold on.
لماذا تجادل مع امرأة بينما
رجل وسيم مثلي هنا؟
Why are you arguing with a woman when
a handsome man like me is right here?
هذا مقابل الإمساك به!
That’s for grabbing him!
"شكرًا لإمساكه"؟
"Thanks for grabbing him"?
اللعنة، على وشك أن يحولوني
إلى ملصق الآن.
Damn, they’re about to turn me
into a poster now.
اهدأ، اهدأ.
Calm down, calm down.
إنها نعمة أن تُضرب
على يد امرأة جميلة!
It’s a blessing to get beaten
by a pretty woman!
يا إلهي، عيناه حمراء!
Oh god, his eyes are blood red!
-مهلاً! ماذا؟ هل أنتم فريق؟
-لا، سيدي!
-Hey! What? Are you two a team?
-No, sir!
-إذا سمع رئيسي عن هذا—
-ماذا سيفعل؟
-If my boss hears about this—
-What will he do?
اتصل به! سأصفعه بحذائي أيضًا!
Call him! I’ll slap him with
my slipper too!
-ماذا؟!
-ستضرب رئيسي؟!
-What?!
-You’ll hit my boss?!
سأقتلكم أنتم الأثنين!
I’ll kill both of you!
-تظن أنني خائف؟
-سوجي! سوجي!
-You think I’m scared?
-Suji! Suji!
ارمِي السكين!
Drop the knife!
لقد أدخلتم شخصًا
في سرير المستشفى بذلك.
You’ve already put someone
in the hospital bed with that.
ألا يمكنك أن تختبئ؟!
Can’t you lay low?!
لقد وضعوا شخصًا بالفعل
في المستشفى؟!
They’ve already put someone
in the hospital?!
يا إلهي!
Oh god!
ما هذا؟ لماذا ضربته
بحذاء؟
What is this? Why did you hit
him with a slipper?
شعرت بالشجاعة لأنك كنت هنا، يا سيدي.
I felt brave because you were here, sir.
بسببي؟
Because of me?
-لم أعلم أبدًا أنك شجاع هكذا، سيدي!
-أنا؟!
-I never knew you were so bold, sir!
-Me?!
رائع، سيد سنجارام!
Super, Singaram master!
رائع، يا سنجارام!
Super, Singaram!
واو… لمسة واحدة منك كافية
لخلاصي.
Wow… Just her touch is enough
for my salvation.
مهلاً!
Hey!
سنجارام، لقد انتهيت.
Singaram, you’re done.
لقد أعددت الأدعية والبوجا
والمهرجان!
You’ve got the prayers, the poojas,
and the festival ready!
الآن، كن مستعدًا لكل شيء، حسنًا؟
Now, you be ready for everything, okay?
أوم شاكثي! بارا شاكثي!
Om Shakthi! Para Sakthi!
هل كل شيء على ما يرام؟
Is everything okay?
كل شيء على ما يرام، سيدي.
Everything is fine, sir.
-حبيبتي، حان الوقت.
-سوري، سأتصل بك لاحقًا.
-Honey, it’s time.
-Soori, I’ll call you later.
امسك هذا.
Hold this.
لا، ضعه على ابن أخي.
No, put it on my brother’s son.
-لماذا؟
-خذه فقط، يا بني.
-Why?
-Just take it, son.
إنه علامة احترام.
It's a sign of respect.
انحنِ برأسك.
Bend your head.
-رئيس...
-احذر.
-Boss...
-Careful.
لا بأس. سنتولى الأمر غدًا.
It’s okay. We’ll handle it tomorrow.
تناول قليلاً.
Have some.
-لا بأس، يا أستاذ.
-لا بأس، خذه فقط.
-It’s fine, teacher.
-It’s okay, just take it.
مر أكثر من أسبوعين منذ
اختفاء راميا.
It’s been over two weeks since
Ramya went missing.
لا تخبر أحدًا،
Don’t tell anyone,
ولكن تلقينا أنباء من
مكتب المفوض أن
but we got word from
the commissioner’s office that
تم تكليف ضابط خاص سريًا.
a special officer has been
secretly assigned.
سيتم العثور عليها.
She will be found.
لم تغب عني حتى ليوم واحد.
She’s never been away from me
for even a day.
الآن، لا أعرف أين هي أو كيف حالها.
Now, I don’t know where she is
or how she is.
الناس يقولون كل الأشياء
في المدينة.
People are saying all sorts
of things in town.
من فضلك، ارسب ابنتي.
Please fail my daughter.
بعد وفاة زوجي،
After my husband passed away,
كنت أقوم بالأعمال المنزلية
لتغطية مصاريف المعيشة.
I’ve been doing household work
to make ends meet.
لست أخجل من قول ذلك،
ليس لدي مال لتعليمها.
I’m not ashamed to say this,
I have no money for her education.
سأدفع رسومها.
I’ll pay her fees.
قد تدفعين عن هذا الشهر،
ولكن ماذا عن الشهر القادم؟
You may pay for this month,
but what about next month?
وماذا عن الذي يليه؟
And the one after that?
لا نريد أن نثقل عليك. لذا رسبها.
We don’t want to burden you. Fail her.
موثاراسو.
Mutharasu.
سبعة وثمانون.
Eighty seven.
راميا.
Ramya.
إذا كنت حقًا تريدين فعل شيء
من أجل والدتك، فادرسي جيدًا!
If you really want to do something
for your mother, study well!
حينها فقط يمكنك الاعتناء بها
كملكة في المستقبل.
Only then can you take care of her
like a queen in the future.
سأرتب لك منحة دراسية.
I’ll arrange a scholarship for you.
ثقي بي، حسنا؟
الآن، ابتسمي.
Trust me, okay?
Now, smile.
-جدي!
-ما الامر يا عزيزتي؟
-Grandpa!
-What is it, dear?
حصلت راميا على كفيل!
Ramya got a sponsor!
لم يعد عليها القلق بشأن
رسوم المدرسة بعد الآن!
She doesn’t have to worry about
school fees anymore!
يجب أن أخبر والدتها فورًا!
I have to tell her mother right away!
يا أستاذ!
Teacher!
هل كانت راميا هنا؟
Has Ramya been here?
في صحتك!
Cheers!
-مهلاً، سينجارام!
-عديم الفائدة.
-Hey, Singaram!
-Useless.
هل هذه حانة أم سكن للمدرسين؟
Is this a bar or the teachers' quarters?
-اصمت، أيها الاصلع.
-مهلاً!
-Shut up, you baldie.
-Hey!
ليس انت. لديك بعض الشعر.
Not you. You've got some hair.
يا استاذة بادما!
Padma teacher!
-ماذا؟!
-اصنعي لنا عجة.
-What?!
-Make us an omelet.
كيف تجرؤون على الشرب واثارة
المشاكل كل يوم في سكن المدرسين؟
How dare you guys drink and cause
trouble every day where teachers live?
انتظر، سأشتكي للمدير!
Wait, I'll complain to the H.M!
المدير؟
The H.M.?
ماذا سيفعل؟
لن يفعل سوى تغريمنا. هذا كل شيء.
What will he do?
He’ll just fine us both. That's it.
مهلاً! لماذا تحدق حفيدتك بغضب؟
Hey! Why is your granddaughter glaring?
من يحدق الآن سيكون
هو من يداعبه لاحقًا.
The one who glares now will be
the one to caress later.
اسمع، لقد كنت تنطق
بهراء كهذا
Listen, you’ve been spewing
nonsense like this
وتشرب الخمر على حسابي.
and guzzling down booze at my expense.
انت لا فائدة منك، يا اجاسو!
You’re of no use, Agasu!
مهلاً! نادني اجاسالينغام.
Hey! Call me Agasalingam.
حقا؟
Is that so?
اذا كنت تريدني ان انطق اسمك بالكامل،
فزوجني حفيدتك.
If you want me to say your full name,
then get your granddaughter married to me.
سأضع اسمك بالكامل اولاً
على بطاقة الدعوة.
I’ll put your full name first
on the wedding card.
لقد شربت خمرا بقيمة ٤٣٥٠٠٠!
You've guzzled down booze worth 4,35,000!
اعد ليّ المال مع الفائدة!
Pay me back with interest!
يبدو هذا الحساب خاطئا.
That math sounds off.
يمكننا تصحيحه لاحقًا.
We can correct it later.
اخبرني اولاً كيف اتزوجها.
First, tell me how to marry her.
تحدث اولاً، ثم اشرب.
Talk first, then drink.
مهلاً! هل انت نائم؟
Hey! Are you sleeping?
لا، انا افكر.
No, I’m thinking.
آه، فكر، فكر.
Oh, think, think.
في شبابي،
كنت اغازل زوجتي بأغنية.
Back in my youth,
I wooed my wife with a song.
-ساعلمك ذلك.
-حسنا.
-I’ll teach you that.
-Alright.
لماذا لا تجرب نفس الشيء؟
Why don’t you try the same?
♪ في قمة كورتالام،
يتأرجح الكركديه.♪
♪ At the peak of Courtallam,
a hibiscus swings.♪
♪ يلمع نظرك مثل
تلألؤ البابايا، يا حبي! ♪
♪ Your gaze shines like
papaya’s gleam, my love! ♪
♪ في قمة كورتالام،
يتأرجح الكركديه.♪
♪ At the peak of Courtallam,
a hibiscus swings.♪
♪ يلمع نظرك مثل
تلألؤ البابايا، يا حبي! ♪
♪ Your gaze shines like
papaya’s gleam, my love! ♪
♪ يلمع نظرك مثل
تلألؤ البابايا، يا حبي! ♪
♪ Your gaze shines like
papaya’s gleam, my love! ♪
♪ يلمع نظرك مثل
تلألؤ البابايا- ♪
♪ Your gaze shines like
papaya’s gleam- ♪
انها تحدق!
She's gazing!
-يا الهي!
-ادخل!
-Oh, my!
-Get in!
اللعنة!
Damn!
سيدي، انه انت؟
Sir, it's you?
كيف عرفت انك ستنقذني؟
How did you know to save me?
زوجتي فعلت الشيء نفسه.
My wife did the same.
على الاقل لم يصب سوى بالماء،
لكنه رش علي ماء روث!
At least he only got water,
she threw dung water on me!
الحب يبدأ دائما بشجار.
Love always starts with a fight.
انا آسف جدا.
I'm so sorry.
لا باس. لم تكن تعرف.
It's okay. You didn’t know.
اخبرتك، اليس كذلك؟
I told you, right?
مهلاً! كان يجب ان يحدث
لي، ليس له!
Hey! That should’ve happened
to me, not him!
كان من الممكن ان تكون تلك لحظتي،
وانت خربتها يا اصلع!
That could’ve been my moment,
and you ruined it, baldie!
قالوا انني استطيع استلام مفتاح منزلي
منك في السكن.
They said I can collect my house key
from you at the quarters.
لقد رحبت بي ترحيبًا لا باس به.
هل هكذا تستقبل الجميع؟
You’ve given me quite the welcome.
Is this how you greet everyone?
لا، يا سيدي.
No, sir.
كنت اصوب نحوهم،
لكنه اصابك عن طريق الخطأ.
I was aiming for them,
but it landed on you by mistake.
تعال، سأحضر مفتاحك.
Come, I’ll get your key.
مهلاً! كان بإمكانه ان يجفف نفسه
بمنشفة.
Hey! He could’ve dried himself
with a towel.
لماذا تفعل ذلك من اجله؟
Why is she doing it for him?
سلوك حفيدتك خرج عن السيطرة!
Your granddaughter’s behavior is
getting out of hand!
مهلاً! هل تشكك في حفيدتي؟
Hey! You’re doubting my granddaughter?
هذا كل شيء! اعتبر هذا طلاقًا
بينكما!
That’s it! Consider this a divorce
between you two!
طلاق؟!
Divorce?!
متى تزوجنا اصلا؟!
When did we even get married?!
صوت تنبيه
beep